thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
how was it?
どうだった?
I'm already done having sex.
もうエッチ終わったけど
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I'm a little tired though.
ちょっと疲れちゃったけど
It was my first time having raw sex, and I even ended up creampieing her.
初めての生エッチで、中出しまでしちゃいましたけど
Well, okay, I said you can cum inside me.
まあまあ、中に出していいよって言ってたから
unintentionally.
つい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
But there were quite a lot of things like this.
でも結構いっぱいこういうの出たじゃん
a little bit...
ちょっと...
OK, but maybe it's okay.
まあまあ、でも多分大丈夫
Much like a man.
多 分大丈夫
That's what I think.
そう思っておきます
To tell you the truth, I'm actually in this room for a moment.
もう言っちゃうと、実はちょっとこの部屋にね、
A friend of mine...
僕の知り合いが...
He came in and I was taking a shower.
入ってきまして、 シャワー浴びてるときにね、
I came in.
入ってきたんです
I'll send you a photo soon,
写真というかね、そろそろ送ったら、
I guess you really want to have sex with me.
ぜ ひエッチしたいっていうかね
Is it mine?
私のですか?
I sent it without permission, but it came by super express.
勝手に送っちゃったけど、 超特急で来たんです
take a look at that person
ちょっと その人のことを見
I want you to give it to me.
せて あげてほしいなって
Are you starting now?
今からですか?
from now.
今から
It's so sudden.
めちゃめちゃ急ですね
It's too sudden though.
急すぎるんだけど
Feeling mount too.
フィーリングマウントも
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
nice to meet you.
はじめまして
It came with great force.
すごい勢いで来た
Look, I'm touching my dick.
ほら見て、チンコ触ってる
I can't stand it.
我慢できないですよ
It's all so sudden.
全部急ですね
That's nice.
いいですね
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いですよね
I agree.
そうですね
Apparently Kana-chan's Instagrammer.
カナちゃんのインスタグラマーらしいですよ
That's right.
そうなんです
Actually, I have it installed as well.
実は僕も、 インストールしてるんです
Haven't you?
してないのか
Well then, please go home.
じゃあ、お帰りください
The condition is that you have it installed.
インストールしてる方が条件なんです
I'm installing it.
インストールしてます
Please install it.
インストールしてね
I want you to follow me.
フォローはなってほしいよね
Please follow me.
フォローしてもらってね
it's okay.
大丈夫です
I'll follow you.
フォローします
I'll follow you, I'll support you,
フォローするんで、応援するんで、
Just a moment with this person, one more time,
ちょっとこの人と、 もう一回ちょっと、
May I?
いいですか?
Are you patient?
我慢か
You don't have to worry about me.
僕のこと気にしなくていいんで
It's okay to have fun.
楽しんじゃっていい
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Do you mean move it a little further back?
ちょっと後ろに寄せたってことですか?
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
It's finally here.
やっとだよね
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Take it out.
出して
There's still a little stage left,
まだちょっとステージが残ってて、
One more time.
もう一回
Can I take it out?
出してもいい?
I might go out.
出 ちゃうかも
Something like this is coming out.
こういうの出てるよ
That's dangerous.
やばいもんね
From the first time.
最初の時より
I came out, but I said something about wanting to cum inside me.
出ちゃったけど、 中に出してみたいなこと言ってたから、
Finally.
ついに
It felt so good that I forgot myself.
気持ちよくて、我忘れちゃった
I see.
そ っか
Did I mention that my spirit was warm?
俺の精神はさ、 温かかったって言ったじゃん?
What happened this time?
今回 どうなった?
It's warm.
温かいの
It was warm too.
温かいもあったから
This amount might be bad.
この量はまずいかもね
It might be bad.
まずいかもね
How many times have you been let out today?
今日何回中に 出されたの?
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎてさ
Well, if it feels good,
じゃあ、 気持ちよかったら、
Kanan cried and said it felt good.
泣 かなし気持ちよかったですって言って
I didn't cry and felt good.
泣かなし気持ちよかったです